[Music]
sup everyone tapers over five here with
a very special video today today is
going to be rather innocent video
because it's not Sonic Underground theme
or rather themed around the Doodlebops
but most importantly a character named
Professor Majorchord you're palling who
the [ __ ] is that
well that's what I was wondering myself
because get this I was looking on the
computer you know the do about for I was
looking through the do box a wiki page
and all of a sudden I saw this post
attorney saying that Professor major
chord was the long-lost uncle I see you
not of the Doodlebops
you're probably wondering what the [ __ ]
I never heard of Professor Majorchord
and neither did I so I went Professor
major codes wiki and that's what he
looks like already something seems very
off about it looks it doesn't look
official I guess he's no fan I'd say he
looks like some random guy you know we a
costume and I did look up he is a real
character he's not running uh but he is
indeed a somebody who played the role of
a character named Professor major called
in a TV show called Kidsongs and there
is something very mysterious going on
and I'm gonna show you what I mean about
this if you scroll all the way down look
at that there are photos of Professor
Majorchord and score even further the
Doodlebops Professor magical will appear
in the drives TV show in the 4th
season where he either all of the
debuffs long-lost uncle pretty normal
right well here's the thing the
Doodlebops never had a 4th season
this guy never did appear
so I was confused I was wondering who
the [ __ ] is he the dogs had a long-lost
uncle that was never revealed I didn't
believe that so I went to the history of
who edited this and I found out that it
is someone named DeeDee doodle
27 and all in the only wikis they follow
Doodlebops in kids songs I clicked on
history and look at that all of the
posts are made from DeeDee doodle
27 going back literally months I neva
mind you something
the Doodlebops ended in 2015 and
Professor Mitch chord that ended in 1998
things could be connected the only made
by the same company do whoever did you
is they are saying the pressing
etiquette of the duo's long-lost uncle I
went to Wycombe Google and saw yes
throughout he does indeed exist he is a
character there is even fan and share of
him on Devon him out I wanted I wanted
to know what is going on so I want to
see how deep this rabbit hole goes and I
did some sleuthing myself and I found
his Facebook page
look how recent this is he made the
account in April 9th of 2018 he only
made six posts two of which are
literally about the doulos what he said
that this is my niece DeeDee doodle
no way even the TV shall do us is he
ever mentioned and I never watched kids
songs but I doubt they would connect to
shows they have no connection and
honestly it starts getting creepy I
found his YouTube channel after very
nice header is a picture of the duo
Bob's he only uploads very creepy ass
low-quality videos of kids shows
if you click about you there you find
nothing so I was one and then all of a
sudden I found out that apparently he
also claims that Angela Grace turns into
DeeDee doodle
from the door so I tapped it in indie
right there on it says Andrew base sad
fall who do about suing as a doodlebop D
do and I just season two intro to the
kids on so I thought okay maybe that
something you back us up I clicked on it
this account has been terminated due to
multiple severe violation of YouTube's
policy against Pam De Ceglie practices
and misleading content of others terms
of violations what the [ __ ] it was what
the [ __ ] and so I was I wanted to find
uncover this mystery myself so I thought
okay I'll look up Angela grace I did and
look at this
Angela grace d-d-duel very stuck out
again and I went down further
I saw the silhouette of a person who is
blacked out in a thumb that called all
about Angela grace Bailey pout one who
the [ __ ] is Angela grace and why the
[ __ ] is a creepy thumbnail of on YouTube
I was I was intrigued then I click on
this video is unavailable I know right
what the [ __ ] is going on I don't know
now I got I got three theories myself
feeling number one he is just a really
big Doodlebops and kids on saying
anything should be really cool if the
two shows what connected nothing wrong
with that but if do not well he is
passing it off as legit when no they do
there is not show three number two he is
some random guy this like is fetes or
some [ __ ]
I don't know doing number three which is
what I believe DeeDee doodle
27 and Professor Majorchord are one and
the same
he wants his job back so he is trying
his damndest to get people talking about
them again he's not doing a good job of
it that's what I believe I believe
Professor Mazur called the I believe
akka is trying to get his job back
and that's what's going on yeah why do I
think that speaker look at this [ __ ]
the only one to [ __ ] edits Professor
mates cause wait wiki page is [ __ ]
d-d-duel 27 he's gotta be that's an
apple look at this I will goody do twice
Evan look at this [ __ ] now watch what
happens I attempt
look at that hat are you [ __ ] kidding
look at that
look look the year - Channel [ __ ] TV
do I upload Professor major card offers
of how to making choices and [ __ ] do you
do it do you guys get what I'm saying